<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://gohugo.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 13:53:58 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://gohugo.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week Four</title>
      <link>http://gohugo.io/blog/weekfour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 13:53:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gohugo.io/blog/weekfour/</guid>
      <description>Day One I am now practicing leetcode to help keep my mind fresh on Data Structures and Algorithms. I am using NeetCode and Abdul Bari on YouTube to help teach me the concepts that I can apply to solve these problems. By doing leetcode, I want to ensure that if I do get interviews, I will have some sort of experience in trying to solve the technical problems given.
I am also steadily going through the Google UX design course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week Three</title>
      <link>http://gohugo.io/blog/weekthree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 12:13:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gohugo.io/blog/weekthree/</guid>
      <description>Day One I went through a bit of the UX Design course but I was out with family the majority of the day.
Day Two I spent most of my time finishing Project: Calculator and have finished the basic features. Tomorrow I will focus on finishing the extra credit portion. I am also slowly going through the Google UX Design course, trying to gather as much knowledge I can for future Front End projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week Two</title>
      <link>http://gohugo.io/blog/weektwo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 14:09:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gohugo.io/blog/weektwo/</guid>
      <description>Day One I started and completed the Project: Landing Page and my solution can be found on my GitHub with the hosted website here.
What I can say from completing this web page is that CSS is very tiresome. Hopefully with enough practice and experience, I will start to like it. I have also started the JavaScript Basics Section For the most part, I have skimmed through the Parts 1 and 2 because I have solid knowledge on the basics of JavaScript As of now, I have almost completed the JavaScript Developer Tools Topic My goals for this section is to finish it as fast as I can because I have faith in my proficiency in programming which includes JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week One</title>
      <link>http://gohugo.io/blog/weekone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 13:17:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gohugo.io/blog/weekone/</guid>
      <description>Day One I have created this portfolio website and blog to showcase my progress to improve my Front End Developer fundamentals.
I spent most of the day configuring this website to host and deploy it on Github Pages.
I have also started the Foundations course from The Odin Project. Although, most of it is Review from previous experience, I felt that it is a good idea start from scratch as it is a good refresher as I may have forgotten some things I learned in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://gohugo.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 09:47:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gohugo.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Mishael Magsanoc and I am a Full Stack Developer.
I specialize in backend development using Java Spring Boot &amp;amp; Express.js and have experience in creating Single Page Applications using React.
I am currently practicing my Front-End Developer fundamentals of HTML5, CSS, and JS using The Odin Project. I am also going through the Google UX Design Certification Course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://gohugo.io/blog/first-post-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 13:05:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gohugo.io/blog/first-post-about/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, this is my first post on my personal blog.
I am currently trying to practice my Front End Developer fundamentals using The Odin Project as I have previously learned Full Stack Development using FullStackOpen. Although, I have learned to create Full Stack applications using Javascript, I believe I am severely lacking in the fundamentals of HTML5, CSS, and JS due to the fact that FullStackOpen uses React at the very start.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
